{
    "id": "2b2adae3c6e24362a222baec7ad08e83",
    "title": "Fill In The Blanks",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The tea was .................................. hot for me to drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6bcdcb63b85744ca95eec096662c1bb6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ................................... arrogant that he will not listen to advice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc0fb1234cfe485f8cb90c604308d02e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked hard ...................................... the examination.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "passing",
                "to pass"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "58d26204a9b9496994cdf6cf9bb66ddf"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is .................................... stupid that he cannot handle such a situation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a7735f224a064cd6a19c8abfe93d3839"
        },
        {
            "question": "John is taller ................................... any other boy in the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "95d23f235dcf472398f2ff4029bb3796"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... trying, I could not do it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "Despite",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "02b9d38f4ae64dd598c4013a6f52abf4"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................... I heard the gunshot I rushed to the spot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "No sooner"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9cdf4fbba1214d9c99161821dc086ba6"
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner had I solved one problem ................................... another cropped up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "when",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3ae155c658d344ecbad83fc81b96aed4"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... trained graduates need to apply.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "None",
                "None other than",
                "None but"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "19d380084ac84d8d9a72914d21076d1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... you do not work hard, you will fail.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "03d5d0dd2fbf48deb5018b3fb72b7715"
        }
    ]
}